http://www.55max.com/pages/privacy-policy

Art Prints
View AllBest SellersJumboValueSets & TriptychsSlim Aarons CollectionSigned & Limited EditionSale
Wallpaper
View AllWallpaper & MuralsMagnetic Write-OnMetallic WallpaperBespoke Wallpaper
Framing & Finishes
Framing Styles & ExamplesFraming InspirationMouldings & StylesPerspex Box FramingMirror FramesPerspex Face MountingPrinted AcrylicPrinted CanvasPrinted WoodPrint on FlooringPrinted Aluminium Dibond
View All
Bestsellers
Originals & Limited Edition
SLIM AARONS COLLECTION
Personalised Images
Bespoke Art Commissions
Gift Vouchers
Oversized Art
My account
SHOP IN:
£
€
$
0
Help
Contact Us
FAQs
Delivery & Returns
Account Login
Favourites
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Cookie Statement
Privacy Policy
www.55MAX.com (“our site”) is owned and operated by Bespoke Photo Design Ltd t/a 55MAX (“55MAX”).
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.This policy applies to you as soon as you first use our site, and you are deemed to have agreed to be bound by this policy upon your first use of our site. If you do not wish to continue to be bound by this policy, please stop using our site now.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Bespoke Photo Design Ltd t/a 55MAX a company registered in England with company number 7175122 and whose address is 186 Willifield Way, London NW11 6YA.
Information we may collect from you
We may collect and process the following data about you:
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, such as your contact details.
We may ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
Details of transactions you carry out through our site.
Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources that you access.
IP addresses
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website and to obtain information about your general internet usage. A cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer and contains information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site, enabling us to deliver a better and more personalised service.
In particular, cookies enable us:
To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests and send you tailored alerts with your consent.
To speed up your searches.
To recognise you when you return to our site.
You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any financial transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
Uses made of the information
We use information held about you in the following ways:
To comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.
To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
To confirm your identity in order to create your account and ensure that you are eligible to use the services provided on our site.
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
To notify you about changes to our service.
Disclosure of your information
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
In the case of third party service providers, solely in the course of their provision of services to us.
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our users will be one of the transferred assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety, and that of our users, or others.
This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes.
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Access to information
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. As soon as you use our site after any revisions are posted, you will be deemed to have agreed to the updated version, but you will still be bound by the terms of any previous versions to which you have agreed or been deemed to agree.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@55MAX.com.
© 2020 55MAX. All rights reserved.
